Guide to the Rick Lang Photographs of Florida and Other Southern States, 1985-2013 RL.11372
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Rick Lang photographs of Florida and other Southern states
1985-2013
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lang, Rick, 1955-2013
RL.11372
12 Linear Feet 13 boxes 229 photographic prints; 258 contact sheets; approximately 3100 negatives; approximately 40 printed items; 130 digital files
Photographer and faculty member at the Creadlé School of Art, Winter Park, Florida. Collection comprises 229 large-format black-and-white photographs by Rick Lang, documenting the communities and landscapes of the American South, with an emphasis on roadside signs, small businesses, and weathered buildings. While the majority of the images were taken in Florida, there also many taken in other states throughout the South, particularly in Louisiana. There are also a few from New Mexico and Arizona. Photographic processes include gelatin silver and pigmented inkjet prints. Print sizes are chiefly 11x14, 13x19, and 16x20 inches, and were printed and signed by the photographer. Accompanying the prints are approximately 3100 negatives and 258 contact sheets linked by unique identification numbers. In addition there is a small amount of print materials chiefly associated with his solo and group exhibits, and condolences sent upon his passing in 2013. Also includes digital files of images. Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Arrangement
Organized into these series: Photographs; Contact Sheets; Negatives; Printed Materials; and Digital Files. All photographic materials are arranged in identification number order as assigned by the photographer.
Biographical Note
Rick Lang was a photographer and long-time faculty member of the Crealdé School of Art in Winter Park Florida, a community-based nonprofit arts organization established in 1975.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of the collection are restricted: original negatives are closed to general use.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Rick Lang photographs of Florida and other Southern states were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2016.
Scope and Contents
Collection contains 229 black-and-white gelatin silver or inkjet large-format prints by photographer Rick Lang, documenting the communities and landscapes of Florida and other Southern states; there are also a few images taken in New Mexico and Arizona. Prints are typically sized 11x14, 13x19, and 16x20 inches, and are signed and printed by Lang. About half are housed in 16x20 and 20x24 inch window mats. The prints are arranged in number sequence as assigned by Lang; the negatives and contact sheets are linked by contact sheet numbers which are noted in each print entry in this collection guide.
Lang's work focuses chiefly on scenes of weathered buildings and businesses - stores, motels, bars, alligator farms, and tourist shops - along the back roads of the South; there are also many photographs of signs and graffiti. Few if any people are present. Among the exceptions is a sequence of images of protesters in Florida demonstrating against censorship and other issues.
Accompanying the prints is a full set of negatives and contact sheets, with many additional images that are not present in the large-format series. There is also a small amount of printed materials chiefly associated with his solo and group exhibits, and condolences sent upon his passing in 2013. Three photograph books offer images not present in this collection of people in the Florida communities where Lang lived and worked. Also includes digital files of about 111 selected images.
Acquired as part of the Archive of Documentary Arts at Duke University.
Advertising, Outdoor -- Pictorial works; Documentary photography -- Florida; Documentary photography -- Louisiana; Documentary Photography -- Southern States; Photographers -- Florida; Florida -- Pictorial works; Louisiana -- Pictorial works; Southern States -- Photographs; Southern States -- Social conditions; Southern States -- Social life and customs; Black-and-white photographs; Contact sheets; Digital prints; Digital images; Gelatin silver prints; Inkjet prints; Negatives (photographs); Archive of Documentary Arts (Duke University); Lang, Rick, 1955-2013
- Photographs, 1990-2013; 1; 10.5 Linear Feet 8 boxes 229 prints
  Arrangement
  Prints are arranged in their original order according to the numerical sequence applied by the photographer. The print number of each print forms part of the institutional identifier.
  Scope and Contents
  Traditional gelatin silver prints are sized either 11x14 (boxes 1-3, matted prints) or 16x20 inches (box 4, matted prints), while the digital inkjet prints are 13x19 inches (boxes 5-6, unmatted). Most of the prints are in 16x20 or 20x24 inch window mats. Sizes in boxes 7-8 are a mix of 11x14 or 16x20 inches - most are matted. Print number 215 is not present in collection and is not present in one version of photographer's inventory.
  - Jesus, Highway 401, North Carolina, 2004 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0001)
    Original contact sheet number: 211
  - Repent Last Call, Murfreesboro, Tennessee, 1999 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0002)
    Original contact sheet number: 84
  - Cindy's Bail Bonds, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 2006 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0003)
    Original contact sheet number: 228
  - Boat ramp sign, north Florida, 2003 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0004)
    Original contact sheet number: 124
  - Round house, Las Vegas, New Mexico, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0005)
    No negative
  - Snorky Love, near Lake Wales, Florida, 2004 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0006)
    Original contact sheet number: 209
  - An Energetic Hula, Charlotte, South Carolina, 2002 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0007)
    Original contact sheet number: 72
  - Cardui sign, Woodbury, Tennessee, 1999 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0008)
  - Storefront, Las Vegas, New Mexico, 1990 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0009)
  - Rubber head, undated (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0010)
  - Bar window, undated (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0011)
  - Girls outside bar, undated (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0012)
  - Bikeweek #8, Daytona Beach, Florida, 1991 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0013)
  - Liquors World, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2000 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0014)
    Original contact sheet number: 158
  - Swampy Giant, US 50, Florida, 2005 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0015)
    Original contact sheet number: 113
  - Oasis Liquor, US 27 South, Florida, 1998 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0016)
    Original contact sheet number: 93
  - Train, Caryville, Florida, 1996 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0017)
    Original contact sheet number: 258
  - Darts and Frosted Mugs, near Dade City, 1996 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0018)
    Original contact sheet number: 79
  - Room addition sign, near Evanston, Florida, 1998 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0019)
    Original contact sheet number: 248
  - Chocolate City, near Tallahassee, Florida, 2006 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0020)
    Original contact sheet number: 144
  - Boy Aint That The Truth, US 27, South, Florida, 1996 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0021)
  - Tourist trap, Tarpon Springs, Florida, 2002 (Box 1, Image RL-11372-P-0022)
    Original contact sheet number: 112
  - Frigidaire, Pahokee, Florida, 1994 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0023)
  - Billboard near Inverness, Florida, 2002 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0024)
    Original contact sheet number: 111
  - Orange sign, near Taft, Florida, 1997 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0025)
  - KKK under a bridge, US 90 near Chattahoochee, Florida, 2003 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0026)
    Original contact sheet number: 133
  - Ma is Back, Bithlo, Florida, 1996 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0027)
    Original contact sheet number: 194
  - Nick Hidu, owner, Nick's Quality Automotive Services, Orlando, Florida, circa 1997 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0028)
    Original contact sheet number: 188
  - Future Home of Love, near Holly Springs, Mississippi, 2006 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0029)
    Original contact sheet number: 115
  - Tool shed, Cross Creek, Florida, 1998 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0030)
    Original contact sheet number: 98
  - Floyd's, High Springs, Florida, 1997 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0031)
  - Diner, New Port News, Virginia, 2001 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0032)
    Original contact sheet number: 224
  - Crack Killed Applejack, Valdosta, Georgia, 2002 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0033)
    Original contact sheet number: 219
  - God Bless America, Bithlo, Florida, 2003 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0034)
    Original contact sheet number: 140
  - Lost Dog, Bithlo, Florida, 2001 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0035)
  - Railroad embankment, Melbourne, Florida, 2002 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0036)
    Original contact sheet number: 153
  - Repent Final Warning, Selma, Alabama, 2000 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0037)
  - Under a bridge, Highway 31, Georgia, 2005 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0038)
    Original contact sheet number: 143
  - Happy B-Day Missy, White Springs, Florida, 2002 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0039)
    Original contact sheet number: 156
  - Beach, Tybee Island, Georgia, 2004 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0040)
    Original contact sheet number: 185
  - Lakeland, Florida, 1999 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0041)
    Original contact sheet number: 175. Image shows Silver Moon drive-in movie theater sign.
  - Jackson County, Florida, 1997 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0042)
    Original contact sheet number: 71. Image shows gas pump outside weathered building.
  - Fill Dirt sign, near Osteen, Florida, 1998 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0043)
  - Sponge and shell display, Tarpon Springs, Florida, 2002 (Box 2, Image RL-11372-P-0044)
    Original contact sheet number: 103
  - Fish Dinner, Caryville, Florida, 2005 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0045)
    Original contact sheet number: 108
  - Cross on tree, north Florida, 2003 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0046)
    Original contact sheet number: 123
  - North Brevard Salvage, near Mimms, Florida, 2007 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0047)
    Original contact sheet number: 159
  - Barber shop, Florida, undated (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0048)
  - Mom & Pop's Place, Bartow, Florida, 2001 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0049)
    Original contact sheet number: 148
  - U.S. 441 near Ocala, Florida, 1999 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0050)
    Original contact sheet number: 135
  - Near Lake Monroe, Florida, undated (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0051)
    Original contact sheet number: 257. Image shows landscape with trees in background.
  - Ghost town, U.S. 66, New Mexico 1996 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0052)
  - Cross, Truchas, New Mexico, 1990 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0053)
  - Champion sign, Leesburg, Florida, 1998 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0054)
  - Country Chat & Chew, north Florida, 2004 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0055)
    Original contact sheet number: 146
  - Soul Food, Helena, Arkansas, 2006 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0056)
    Original contact sheet number: 152
  - BarBQue smoker, Ft. Pierce, Florida, 1999 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0057)
    Original contact sheet number: 139
  - Fireworks, Alabama, 2006 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0058)
    Original contact sheet number: 137
  - Bus stop near Betsy Layne, Kentucky, 1995 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0059)
    Original contact sheet number: 227
  - Watermelon sign, Southern Tennessee, 1999 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0060)
    Original contact sheet number: 208
  - Wholesale Batteries, McMinnville, Tennessee, 1999 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0061)
    Original contact sheet number: 218
  - Dangerous words, circa 1990 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0062)
    Original contact sheet number: 251. Image shows protest march sign, "Only the suppressed word is dangerous."
  - Protect, circa 1990 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0063)
    Original contact sheet number: 250. Image shows people with U.S. flag under a columned portico of a large building, while someone is being interviewed by the media.
  - Flag, circa 1990 (Box 3, Image RL-11372-P-0064)
    Original contact sheet number: 249. Image shows two men, one holding flag, the other holding sign, "Ye must be born again."
  - First Amendment #1, Orlando, Florida, 1990 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0065)
    Original contact sheet number: 250. Image shows protesters marching with sign, "Central Floridians against censorship."
  - Junkyard, Pahokee, Florida, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0066)
  - CSX office, Okeechobee, Florida, 2010 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0067)
    Digital file (no contact sheet)
  - Sand Dollar, Highway 441, Florida, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0068)
  - Pool hall, Bartow, Florida, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0069)
  - South Port Paints, Eufalla, Alabama, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0070)
  - Closed car repair, Okeechobee, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0071)
  - Harvey's Groves, Rockledge, Florida, 2010 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0072)
  - Rot Pit Pups for Sale, Alexandria, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0073)
  - Football field, Bogalusa, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0074)
  - Ice machine, north Louisiana, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0075)
  - Oil pump in corn field, northern Louisiana, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0076)
  - Broken Spoke Ranch, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0077)
  - Motel Closed, US 19, near Perry, Florida, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0078)
  - U Pick, north Florida, 2003 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0079)
    Original contact sheet number: 99
  - Hay For Sale, north Florida, 2003 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0080)
    Original contact sheet number: 121
  - Carnival sign, Baker, Florida, 2003 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0081)
    Original contact sheet number: 221
  - Greens 4 Sale, north Florida, 2003 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0082)
    Original contact sheet number: 125
  - Wheel balancer, Okeechobee, Florida, undated (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0083)
  - Rock & Roll Men's Store, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0084)
  - Dance studio, Crescent City, Florida, 2009 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0085)
  - Ice House, Avon Park, Florida, 2008 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0086)
  - Auto Parts, Bithlo, Florida, 1996 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0087)
    Original contact sheet number: 138
  - Dawson Tire Co., Dawson, Georgia, 2011 (Box 4, Image RL-11372-P-0088)
  - Happy Trails, Alexandria, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0089)
  - Turkey Shoot, near Tampa, Florida, 2005 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0090)
    Original contact sheet number: 205
  - Dismal Swamp, North Carolina, 2007 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0091)
    Original contact sheet number: 216
  - Ice box, Crescent City, Florida, 2009 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0092)
    Digital file (no contact sheet). This matted print has been separated from the unmatted prints, and is housed in box 7 with other similar sized items.
  - Fan & wheel, Lake Alfred, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0093)
  - South of The Border, South Carolina, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0094)
  - Old motel, US 27 South, central Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0095)
  - Southhampton Taxidermy, Virginia, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0096)
  - Handle under Tension, Tavares, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0097)
  - Catfish, central Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0098)
  - Indian Head, near Suffolk Virginia, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0099)
  - Quality Meats, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0100)
  - Open 8-8, crossroads, Highway 50, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0101)
  - Modern Day Furniture, West 17-92, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0102)
  - Dollars, Casselberry, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0103)
  - Trucks Do Not Enter, Hastings, Florida, 2012 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0104)
  - Auto-Truck Alignment, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0105)
  - Main Disconnect, Wildwood, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0106)
  - Closed train, Tavares, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0107)
  - Williston Peanuts, Inc. plant, Williston, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0108)
  - Tree & wall, crossroads, Highway 50, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0109)
  - Lawn sculpture, Virginia, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0110)
  - Spot Pool Hall, Alexandria, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0111)
  - Store front, Leesburg, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0112)
  - Grandview Motel, Ft. Pierce, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0113)
  - Philips Music, Polk County, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0114)
  - Luv, Eau Gallie, Florida, 2013 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0115)
  - Gift shop, north Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0116)
  - Butch's BBQ, south Georgia, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0117)
  - Get Hose and Soap, Lake Alfred, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0118)
  - J.J.s Deli, Highway 61, Mississippi, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0119)
  - Motorcycles Too, near Sanford, Florida, 2010 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0120)
  - BF Goodrich, Okeechobee, Florida, 2010 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0121)
  - Peanut plant, Williston, Florida, 2011 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0122)
  - Todd Bertolaet, Kissimmee, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0123)
  - Big Fishing Worms, Lake Rosemary, Florida, 2007 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0124)
  - Highway 27, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0125)
  - No Animals, Crescent City, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0126)
  - Pawn & Alterations, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0127)
  - Beer & Breakfast, Highway 60, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0128)
  - Butch's BBQ #2, South Georgia, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0129)
  - City Coney Island, Monroe, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0130)
  - Bar, Mamou, Louisiana, 2009 #2 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0131)
  - Gator Farm, along US 1, central Louisiana, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0132)
  - Church yard, southeast Louisiana, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0133)
  - US 50, near Titusville, Florida, undated (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0134)
  - South Hampton Taxidermy Shop, Virginia, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0135)
  - Shuffleboard courts, Kissimmee, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0136)
  - Auto Repair, Brooksville, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0137)
  - Pahokee, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0138)
  - Motel sign, Dundee, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0139)
  - Fan & window, Micanopy, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0140)
  - Barbecue stand, US 27, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0141)
  - Helena Fish Market, Helena, Arkansas, 2007 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0142)
  - Equivalents, Kitty Hawk, North Carolina, 2007 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0143)
  - Old gas pump, Center Hill, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0144)
  - Wall abstraction, White Springs, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0145)
  - Angel, Daytona Beach, Florida, 2007 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0146)
  - Woodies Hat Box, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2009 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0147)
  - Parking, St. Cloud, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0148)
  - Garage door, Brooksville, Florida (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0149)
  - Where the fountain of youth dried up, St. Augustine, Florida, 2008 (Box 5, Image RL-11372-P-0150)
  - Wall, White Springs, Florida, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0151)
  - No Trespassing, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0152)
  - Broken window, Virginia, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0153)
  - Indian Mound Fish Camp, A1A, Florida, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0154)
  - Cheap Tree Work, Dundee, Florida, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0155)
  - Tompkins Cemetery, north Florida, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0156)
  - Repos, north central Florida, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0157)
  - Hurt Paint, Georgia, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0158)
  - Bridge column, Arcadia, Florida, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0159)
  - Peanut plant #1, Franklin Virginia, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0160)
  - Angry bunny, White Springs, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0161)
  - Peppers, Rockledge, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0162)
  - B-Ball court, south Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0163)
  - Catfish Bend, U.S. 1, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0164)
  - BF Goodrich Tires, Okeechobee, Florida, 2011 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0165)
  - Hicks Superette, Clarksdale, Mississippi, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0166)
  - Volunteers, Richmond, Virginia, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0167)
  - Highway 60, Florida, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0168)
  - Tanks, power plant, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0169)
  - Harvey's #3, Rockledge, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0170)
  - Truck, Sterlington, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0171)
  - Wall, Okeechobee, Florida, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0172)
  - Peanut plant #2, Franklin, Virginia, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0173)
  - Kirk Welding, Monroe, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0174)
  - Blue Bird, Valano Beach, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0175)
  - No Children, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0176)
  - Complete Detailing, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0177)
  - Harvey's Groves #2, Rockledge, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0178)
  - Anchor, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0179)
  - Graffiti, Richmond, Virginia, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0180)
  - Oasis, U.S. 27 South, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0181)
  - C&L Feed, northeast Florida, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0182)
  - Game Room, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0183)
  - Peanut shop, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0184)
  - Bowling alley, Winter Garden, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0185)
  - Flow Master window, Okeechobee, Florida, 2010 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0186)
  - Sardis Community Hunting Club, Louisiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0187)
  - Jesus Will Return, R U Ready, northeast Louisiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0188)
  - New Hope Baptist Church, Slidell, Lousiana, 2009 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0189)
  - No Parking, Valdosta, Georgia, 2002 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0190)
  - Self Serv, Yeehaw Junction, Florida, 2001 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0191)
  - Live Alligators, US 27, south Florida, 2012 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0192)
  - Wall, Georgia, 2008 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0193)
  - & Meats, Crossroads Highway 50, Florida, 2009 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0194)
  - I Love St. Pete, St. Petersburg, Florida, 2009 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0195)
  - Jane's Place, south Florida, 1996 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0196)
    Original contact sheet number: 164
  - Freedom is a State of Mind, Palatka, Florida, 2002 (Box 7, Image RL-11372-P-0197)
  - Land developer's Airstream trailer, north Florida, 2007 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0198)
    Original contact sheet number: 106
  - Fertilizer plant, Lake Alfred, Florida, 1995 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0199)
  - Post office, Livingston, South Carolina, 1993 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0200)
  - White house, Prestonburg, Kentucky, 1995 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0201)
  - Space Balls, The Boardwalk, Daytona Beach, Florida, 2004 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0202)
  - Confederate statue, Bainbridge, Georgia, 1998 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0203)
    Original contact sheet number: 212
  - Hot Dog stand, Daytona Beach, Florida, 2005 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0204)
    Original contact sheet number: 109
  - Keep Out or Get shot, near Deland, Florida, 2004 (Box 6, Image RL-11372-P-0205)